A Guide to the William Stanley Braithwaite Collection, 1899-1928, n.d.
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
- Miscellaneous Material
  - Proofs of some of the anthologies, etc. (All that remains), 3 folders (Box 12-13)
    - Anthology of Magazine Verse for 1926, edited by William Stanley Braithwaite with editorial corrections 1926, Galley Proof (Box 12)
    - Biographies of Poets of Anthology of Magazine Verse for 1926, edited by William Stanley Braithwaite 1926, Galley Proof (Box 12)
    - Essays from Anthology of Magazine Verse for 1926 1926, Galley Proof (Box 12)
    - The Book of Georgian Verse, edited by William Stanley Braithwaite 1908, Page Proofs (Box 12)
    - "Yearbook of American Poetry," from Anthology of Magazine Verse for 1928, edited William Stanley Braithwaite 1928, Galley Proofs (Box 12)
    - "Biography," by J. Masefield from The Forumn.d., Galley Proof (Box 12)
  - The Spirit of Transportation Poetry Prize Contest (William Stanley Braithwaite was a judge) (Box 13)
  - Additional Papers of William Stanley Braithwaite, ca. 1910-1940, 10 AMS, 1 TLS, printed order forms (Box 13)